Jyothi Hadimani

+91 9148865060 <u>iyothi.hadimani@gmail.com</u> https://www.linkedin.com/in/jyothich/



Kev Skillsets

- Complex Project Management
- · Stakeholder Management
- Agile and Scrum Methodology

Work Experiences

- PwC India 2017 to Till Date
- L&T Technologies Bangalore – 2014 to 2016
- L&T Infotech 2009 to 2013 (India, Japan)
- Wipro India 2006 to 2008
- TCS 2004 to 2006 (Sweden, India)
- Nikkel India 2000 to 2003

Education

- BE (E&C) from PESIT Bangalore
- Certificate in PMP from PMI
- Certificate in CSM from Scrum Alliance
- Certificate from IIM Calcutta in Women Leadership
- AWS Partner Certificate Economics Accreditation Issued by AWS
- Telecom Training from University of Stockholm

Reference

Reference Available on request.

Background

Jyothi s currently working as Manager with PwC in India and has over 16 years of experience in Project Management. An Astute Thinker Leader, Planner, and Implementer with proven management skills across various domains including Consumer electronics, Mobile and Government and Public Sector.

Professional and Industry Experience

PMP Certified Expert and Women Leader with relevant Certification from IIM Calcutta, she has the ability to drive the team and deliver successfully and efficiently. Knowledgeable about the Agile Methodology, attempting to provide through utilizing leadership expertise.

Current Role

As a Principal Consultant, I oversee implementing and directing the project from requirement gathering through onboarding the services via the portal for one of the government of Karnataka's citizen-centric initiatives. The goal is to give Karnataka residents easily accessible, cost effective, responsible, and transparent government services.

Other clients I worked for are

- GSTN (Goods and Service Tax Network) and Commercial tax department of Government of Karnataka
- BMTC (State owned public road transport corporation, Bangalore) For Business process Re-engineering

Select Prior Experiences

- In My role as Scrum Master, I oversaw a team of 25 middleware developers who were
 working with Cisco team to develop Set Top Box for Verizon operator. Agile
 methodology was used for new feature development, bug fixing and maintance.
- Successfully Lead the team for providing the stability and performance improvement of the Symbian OS Mobile Phones of Sony Ericsson (OEM) at Tokyo Japan Before the launch of the new Products
- As a team member I was in charge of developing, testing, bug fixing and supporting Triton Drivers for Texas Instrument chips (Omap 2430 and Omap 3430) used in the manufacture of Symbian OS based Mobile devices
- As a team member I was responsible for new feature development, testing, support and maintainace of one of the module FMS (File Management System) of Ericsson's AXE switch at Stockholm Sweden.
- I was part of the team developing various algorithms and sticky notes.

Awards And Achievements

- Prime Minister Award 2021 for the Project on citizen centric services (PwC)
- Above and Beyond Award-Team 2022 (PwC)
- Platinum award of the year 2014 (L&T Technology Services)
- The Best Performance Team 2010 award (L&T Infotech)
- Participated in Tokyo Marathon and won Medal (2011)